Okay, the time is already 35 minutes, so let's get started.
I don't know if you guys know what the theme of today's video is.
Today, our theme for this video is...
Hannah's...
Hannah's dress.
Let me find it.
Hello, good evening everyone.
Hannah's dress.
It's this one.
This one is a dress.
So let's get started.
This is a video I've already recorded.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Sherry.
I'm a designer at Marvelous Design.
Today, I'm going to show you how to make a dress.
First, we're going to use the 3D drawing function to draw a circle on the virtual model.
Oh, my camera is blocking my screen.
And then after you're done, you can take a look.
In the process of drawing, press the Ctrl key.
Then you can draw a straight line.
Why do we need to draw this circle?
It's because we're going to...
For example, now we're going to make the circle flat.
After that, we're going to use this circle as a base.
We're going to add some fabric on top of it.
This way, the shape won't change.
Okay, and then we're going to arrange it at the 3D window.
Then we're going to use the tool called Flatten.
Oh, okay.
Next time, I'm going to show you how to do that.
Thank you.
Thank you for sharing the live stream.
After that, I'm going to add some pins to the two ends of this circle.
Because after we've created the template,
this template doesn't necessarily match our model.
Turn it on.
This is a video I recorded in advance.
Don't let me turn off the material.
After that, I'm going to turn on the simulation.
And then...
This is a bit tied to me.
Okay, now I can finally see it clearly.
And then I'm going to change the position of this fixer.
Adjust the position of this steel ring.
So that it can fit the chest line of our model.
Okay.
After that, we can freeze these two panels.
After that, we're going to use these two panels as a basis.
Create some panels between them.
Whether you're doing some swimsuits or doing some close-up clothing,
it's best to have two steel rings like this as a basis.
So that you don't have to change your posture or do any other movements.
There won't be any changes.
Okay.
And then I'm going to draw other panels along the body line of the virtual model.
Like doing this kind of tight outfit.
We usually draw the basic panels directly on the virtual model.
And then it's the same.
After that, we're going to flatten this piece.
After flattening it,
you can see how many panels there are in the 2D window.
And then we're going to make it into a symmetrical panel.
After flattening,
I'm going to start looking at the shape of this panel.
I was going to do some more unique designs for it.
And then I'm going to divide the area on the model to hook the curve.
If you usually use it, you can actually draw it directly.
You don't need to split it like I did.
Just split the front and back.
You see, I'm going to start drawing the back.
For this kind of tight outfit,
you can draw it on the model.
And then it's the same.
Flatten it into a panel.
And delete some unnecessary curve points.
And then after you're done with the curve points,
I'm going to start checking if this side panel can be aligned.
I found that this can't be aligned,
so I'm going to change its size.
After finishing the changes,
the side panel's size is pretty much aligned.
It's a little bit of a loop.
After it's aligned,
I'm going to use Ctrl D to add a layer on it.
It's an even layer.
It's the same as the side panel.
That is, the symmetrical version of the string.
After that, create the sewing line again.
After creating it, there is something I want to tell you.
It's like this smaller version.
You can reduce the strength of it as early as possible.
When I freeze this steel ring version,
I can make some adjustments to other parts.
In fact, it is equivalent to now I have a piece of area.
This steel ring is like a steel body.
It is the foundation of your whole swimsuit.
So from beginning to end,
basically these two steel rings,
when you see it, it won't move.
Then combine the sides.
Thank you for your attention.
Then we reduce the conflict thickness a little bit.
It can make it easier for you
to stick the skin of the virtual model tightly.
And before that,
we lowered the surface diameter of the virtual model.
When you are making tight clothing,
you must remember to reduce the surface diameter
and the conflict thickness of the board.
This way, you can stick the virtual model tightly.
Then drag the position of the board.
Why do you send love messages?
To allow you to see the view of the virtual model.
In order to make it easier.
And then we will start.
Oh yes, I find that...
Okay okay.
I found that the curve in the front
seemed not ideal.
It's okay.
Then adjust it again.
As long as our live streamer is still there, there should be no problem. If the live streamer is not there, then I will leave it open.
Then use the round-shape curve to round this area.
After almost adjusting it, freeze this part. Now we are going to do the upper part.
Do the same on the back. Draw a line on the virtual model.
You can draw according to the shape you want, along the body curve of the virtual model.
After drawing, flatten it into a board.
Then you can see that there is a basic board.
Next, you have to align it.
You can see the length of the two lines at the bottom.
The length here is because the face is relatively large.
You can see that the board is a little big.
It's loose when you put it on.
We'll have to deal with this later.
Do the same on the back.
Then draw a parallel board.
You can see that there will be some wrinkles after sewing.
We are going to make a change to these two boards.
Because we are going to use these two boards as the base layer.
We are going to change the length of the sides.
Then let these two boards take off.
So that they can stick to the virtual model's skin.
Then it's kind of wrapped up.
Then we have to...
Ah!
The supervisor warned me.
Hello, hello, supervisor.
There's nothing we can do about this.
This is our setting.
Hello, hello, hello.
Is the live broadcast room still on?
This is what our software looks like.
Oh my god.
No way.
Hello, supervisor.
I'm sorry, supervisor.
This is what our software looks like.
Okay, okay, okay.
You scared me.
No, no.
But this is a video that I recorded in advance.
Oh my god.
Then let's change this virtual model's...
Oh, I'm so nervous.
Okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay.
I think it should be okay.
Supervisor, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Then...
Then let's change this physical attribute of the board.
After changing the physical attribute to the skin,
the board will be a little more...
Sorry, sorry.
I don't want to challenge the supervisor.
I'm sorry.
Apologize to the super bowl first.
This is the setting of our software.
Then go to the back of the shoulder strap.
This is Iris Designer 10.
Then use the 3D sewing tool
to sew the back in the 3D window.
After sewing the back in the 3D window,
you can see that I have added two pins first.
This can prevent the shoulder strap from being misaligned.
Adjust it a little bit.
Adjust it.
After that, you can see that the two front panels are stretched.
I didn't expect that.
I actually thought of it after I finished it.
But I don't think it's very real.
I don't think it's very real.
I didn't expect to be able to pass the warning so early.
I thought it wasn't natural.
But you can see it.
I also think.
Here, I want to tell you about this part.
The fabric part is made of leather.
Viewers may see some wrinkles in the lower chest area.
But now it's not.
We can use leather
when we practically make the master stay.
the material properties
and then make some adjustments
like the shape of the board
I'll skip this part
skip this part
speed up
I'm so nervous after doing this
next are some changes
about the basic shape
changes
material properties changes
on the right side of the plant window
select a plant
and in the property editor below
you can edit it
then I might use a sewing needle
to sew the basic board
to the model
so that it can stick to the skin
then I'll do some adjustments
to the model
like adding a line
and then
a layer of the pattern
using the line
to divide it
because
I want to do some designs
for it
on our
Hannah's
clothes
I made some
you can see
like here
I made some
draw effects
so it actually has two layers
one layer is the basic
which is
it has
a flat layer inside
which is what we did at the beginning
on the back and the outside
I'll give it a cologne layer
and then this layer of cologne
I'll give it
extension
to make it into a larger board
then we sew the big board
and the small board together
there will be some creases
after that
I'll re-create the sewing line
because these two layers are stacked together
so our sewing line on the side
its sewing line type
needs to be changed to turn
after that
I'll adjust the sewing line
I'll sew the two ends
equally long together
a short section in the middle
and a long section in the middle
together
and then
the front
there will be no creases
on the long side
there will be more creases
in the middle
because
I've made the creases
that will be
slightly
too big
so that
we can
sew them together
and then
we'll sew the other side
together
turn around
and then
this way
we'll see
if we can
sew the other side
and then
we'll sew the other side
together
right
so
this is
the end
of the sewing line
I'll show you
how to do it
for the creases
It's often used on clothes that are too tight or tight for other people.
You should have seen it just now.
If you add a collar, it will become more flat on the side soon.
After that, it's...
What am I doing here?
Oh, I think the fold is not ideal.
So I'm adjusting it.
I want it to be more forward.
As you can see, when I use the Custom Angle,
the breastplate will shake all the time.
But if I change to Turn, it won't shake.
So when you're dealing with this kind of two-layer,
because this is a two-layer outfit now,
and there's another layer in it.
When dealing with this kind of multi-layer structure,
the seam line on the side must be changed to Turn.
Are you listening carefully?
Are you listening carefully, guys?
There's no chat all of a sudden. I'm so flustered.
Then merge the two layers.
You can see that there is a merge of the version.
After merging the version,
because the grid of the version after merging,
they have also been changed.
So...
So you have to re-match it with the ruler.
The difference between the types of seam lines is just like that.
One is even.
What about two versions?
Like this position is even.
They are both in the same level.
They belong to the same level.
Then the type of seam line is the top and bottom.
They are stacked together.
We have a fan seal.
The top and bottom stacked together
is called Turn.
Turn is like being flattened.
This will be more stable.
Of course, you can also remember to add our QQ group.
Add the QQ group.
If you have any questions you don't understand,
you can ask directly in the QQ group.
For example, look now.
Is it on top of the two layers?
Then we will change its type to Turn.
Okay, select a group of seam lines with the editor line tool.
After the editor line,
you can change its type of seam line to Turn
in the attribute editor.
Is there a good way to make a flap?
Either use piping,
which is our chain tool.
Or...
Use the other three points.
You can change the previous version.
The old version and the new version
all have the type of seam line.
In addition, I will add a fixing pin
on the whole board.
Then there is a fixing pin on the top edge of the board.
After adding the fixing pin,
this fixing pin will follow the virtual model.
After following the virtual model,
it means that
when our HANA
does action or animation,
it will follow the virtual model.
This means that
when our HANA
does the animation,
this area will not change anymore.
Because it is already
on the point of the virtual model.
It will not move anymore.
Of course, it is not really on the point of the virtual model.
It is just on the point of the virtual model.
It is on the point of the virtual model.
Since the window came,
I suddenly became very nervous.
I am very afraid.
Then I changed its curve.
But I think it should be fine at the back.
It should be better at the back.
Then I freeze it.
Re-activate virtual model.
Why do we need to re-activate the virtual model here?
In fact, the re-activation
is to add the fixing pin
and then right-click
to attach the fixing pin to the virtual model.
That's it.
The reason why we re-activate
the virtual model here is that
we want to make a butterfly knot
on the chest.
The fixing pin
is not yet...
Okay, okay.
Draw a board.
After drawing the board,
arrange its position.
Quickly select one side
and double click on the side.
There is a point here that I want to tell you.
It doesn't let me pause.
Now our virtual model
is hidden by me.
In fact, the virtual model
is re-activated by me.
Because everyone
when dealing with this kind of knotting
must feel that
sometimes
if you knot,
this cloth will definitely
pass through the virtual model's body.
But when it passes through
the virtual model's body,
if your virtual model
is not re-activated, then this board
will definitely collide with the virtual model.
Then it will be very unstable
and not easy to knot.
So in this case,
we will usually
re-activate the virtual model.
Okay.
Then
add two fixing pins to the top and bottom.
After knotting,
we usually just
drag this fixing pin
to knot it.
When knotting,
this knotting
should not be very obvious.
Once the fabric starts to slip,
you need to adjust
its length.
Why does my video
look like this length
is perfect?
Because when it is not perfect,
it is deleted by me.
Thank you.
Okay.
Then add some fixing pins.
Here, why
my knot does not slip?
Because I just
put the knot
in its physical property.
There is a value called friction at the bottom.
I have increased the friction.
So no matter how I adjust
this knot,
it is not easy to slip.
Then,
drag these two fixing pins.
You need to pause the video
and do some processing.
For example,
I added some fixing pins to it.
I am speeding up too fast.
I still use the fixing pins
to add them on both sides.
When you are editing,
press the W button
and the left button
to add the fixing pins.
It is faster than adding the fixing pins manually.
And it is easier to operate.
Yes,
it is faster than adding the fixing pins manually.
Because I do not like
the feeling of turning.
After that,
I will continue to add some fixing pins.
Oh, not fixing pins.
Fixing pins.
If you add the fixing pins,
you can fix the shape of a board.
It is easy to wear the knot.
One is that the diameter of your board
is not small enough.
Another one is that
when you knot,
you must add a lot of fixing pins.
Then,
when your board
is more stable,
you can tighten it.
Once you see that
the material of the board is shaking,
then you should not tighten it.
Now,
when we are finished,
because we have reduced the force to 80 before,
after that,
we can see
if we added the fixing pins.
First of all,
if you want to add the fixing pins
on one side,
we should double-click a dot
and add it along this side.
Before that,
let me go back to the previous step.
the slope of the tail is 80.
That is to say,
the width of the horizontal line
becomes 80% of the original width.
Then it may only be a little wider.
In this case,
we have made this knot.
And add a loop around it
to fix it.
After adding the fixing pins,
will this area be fixed?
Will it not move anymore?
The grid will be here.
At this time,
if we change the width of the horizontal line
from 80 to 100,
will the material in the middle stack up?
Because their area
is fixed in this area.
We can take a look.
After increasing the width of the horizontal line,
we can see
that there are some folds here.
See?
There are also some folds here.
If we do it this way,
we can control
the folds of the material.
In fact,
when I started
to simulate it directly,
its fold shape
was scattered.
So I will choose
to add a fixing pin in the middle
and let both sides
simulate it separately.
Then the shape
will be more natural.
Have you learned it?
If you have learned it,
put it on the public screen.
If you haven't learned it,
watch the live broadcast again.
Today's live broadcast is
relatively fast.
In the following live broadcast,
we will have a teaching video.
In the teaching video,
we will talk about how to operate
and what the fixing pin is.
In the teaching video,
I recorded it first
and then Jimmy added the subtitles.
So,
you should be able to follow it.
And there is no acceleration.
Don't mention the tuition fee.
I'm so stressed.
It's very simple.
You just need to
follow the video without
the acceleration.
You can learn it.
You can definitely learn it.
And then,
I made some internal lines for him.
I sewed the internal lines together.
Because I think there are a lot of
clothes
that have that edge.
I added it for him.
The live broadcast is probably at 9 o'clock.
Around 9 o'clock.
And then I freeze the other panels
and put them back in the middle.
And then I want to add some
designs for him.
I'll draw a rectangle first.
Okay.
And then let's see
what's next.
Next,
add the edge of the river.
Why is the edge of the river
upside down here?
Where do I need
the double sides?
Well,
it depends on you.
Because
for the double sides,
you have to draw the thickness.
Calculation method.
MD10
used to have this calculation method.
I don't know.
Are you talking about GPU?
Does the internal line have a定ative function?
Sometimes it does.
If you add a folding angle to it,
here,
because of the length of the panel,
the internal line is long,
so if you directly simulate it,
there will be such an edge of the river effect.
So,
it depends on you.
Because,
if you make a single side,
you will definitely
draw it with a thin thickness.
Then,
if you make a double side,
you usually have to
bring the thickness out.
Or,
otherwise,
the horizontal line on your side
will not look real.
And for the double side,
the two sides you usually understand
may not be the same.
Add a negative pressure here.
Because,
after our fabric and other fabrics
are sewn together,
it will stand up.
Then,
if you add a negative pressure,
it is equivalent to a pressure.
From here to the inside,
press this circle and side
to the model.
I usually do multi-layer
because, for example, I have a base layer.
Its width or length
is relatively small.
Then, if you make a bigger layer
on the outer layer,
will it have a lot of wrinkles
coming out?
There are some natural wrinkles
because the size of the panel
is different.
It will look more real.
After that,
I will start to make the swimming trunks.
I will directly
draw the swimming trunks here.
I will follow the shadow.
Then,
I will slightly change its length.
I will change its shape.
I always feel that it is very dangerous here.
It is a little dangerous.
For the swimming trunks,
you can directly sew in 3D.
Because I am used to sewing,
I am a little scared
when I speak now.
Then,
I will immediately
reduce the density.
Yes.
Generally,
for a layer,
for a bag,
it is like this.
I used to make bags like this.
Especially,
usually,
this kind of bag
is full of alcohol.
It usually has a lot of details.
Thank you for your attention.
Thank you.
If there is a wrinkle on the second layer,
the authenticity of the bag
will increase.
Then,
here are some
adjustments to the size.
Then,
I want to add some details to it.
I am thinking about this
swimming trunks.
Should I make two bags for it?
Yes.
When I usually do it,
I will
look around.
For example,
what is the trend now?
Or what are the clothes in the animation?
Then,
I will
combine their elements.
I will add some details to it.
Then,
I will
make a 3D seam.
I will sew it.
Then,
I will add some detail to it.
I will add some details to it.
Hello, hello.
Hi, everyone.
I am back.
Hello, hello.
It should be okay now.
I already put a coat on it.
Don't kill me anymore, I'm really scared
Hello? Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Thank you!
Thank you for the delivery of the set meal
Then let's continue to the next section
Is Superstition here?
Hello hello Superstition, thank you Superstition
It's okay, thank you Superstition, thank you Superstition
It's okay, I don't know, I just feel that if I talk like this, Superstition won't block me
Thank you Superstition, it's okay
Let's go to the next section, which is to add a jacket for her
No, because this is a video that I recorded beforehand
And there's no way to add anything else
I'll quickly go to the last section
Then after I'm almost done, I'll add a jacket for her
Superstition, I'm sorry, don't block me anymore
Don't kill me anymore
Okay
Then after that, I'll add a sewing needle for her
To sew her clothes
Then sew the sewing needle onto the model
In this way, her clothes will be sewn in this position
The corresponding position
Oh my god
I see that the popularity here is always 1
I'm going to cry
It's okay
Then change the fabric properties
After changing the fabric properties
Oh oh oh oh
Let's go to the next section
Okay, now it's starting to be a swimming ring
The clothes were just added
Because I'm sorry, because the superstition came just now
It's okay, it's okay
Okay, now I'm going to sew the clothes
Thank you, my mom
Mom's hair
Oh, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay
It doesn't matter if it's popular
Then the version that comes out
Add some pressure for him
After applying pressure
You can see that he has some wrinkles
These wrinkles are caused by natural pressure
When we put pressure on the bigger one
Because of the more gas added in the middle
So these wrinkles will be eliminated
然后内层也是一样,然后压力一定要记得是正负平衡的,千万不要正负不平衡,或者说是给他们用同一项的压力。
因为正向的压力是从内向外去冲压,负的压力是从外向内去冲。
通过这一面我们可以看到上面这个板片是正面朝外,下面那个板片是背面朝外的,所以一个要正压一个要负压。
然后给它外圈加个弹性。
加完弹性之后,
这里面就会有一些抽褶的效果了。
可以看到吗?这里就会有一些抽褶的效果了。
因为我们刚刚改了面料的属性嘛。
可以翻转的,选中板片之后右键有一个表面翻转。
增加摩擦是在,稍等一下。
加摩擦是在选中面料之后下方的物理属性编辑器里面会有。
然后呢,画一下内部线。
这里我都很害怕。
我有B站账号,但是我的B站账号不能发出来。
然后就查看一下长度。
反激活虚拟模特。
接下来就是安全地带了呢。
轻松了许多。
就是像这种泳池板片的话呢。
因为一般来说橡胶它是只有在缝合处比较容易抽褶。
所以我们会选择把面料的物理属性降到特别特别低。
就是经纬杀强度、弯曲强度都降低一些。
这样你去给它充气的时候它的褶皱就几乎都没有了。
然后再给它外圈增加弹性就会。
就会。
有些自然的缝线的效果。
我现在真的有点怕。
是谁发现了我的B站账号?
就算知道我的B站账号也不要发出来。
然后把它的底边缝一下。
有人能猜出来我在做什么吗?
我其实刚刚好像不小心已经说出来我在做什么。
这个头头这里是新加坡斯里。
这个名字很像我一个好友的名字。
改一改物理属性。
对,是额头。
不是尾巴,是头。
其实我本来是想让你们猜我在做什么东西的。
但是你们怎么都在猜这是哪个部位啊?
马上就猜出来这些吧。
放下米粒。
现在这是什么了?
这个小手。
这什么!
这是什么呢?
什么?
什么呀?
什么事啊?
什么是什么?
什么事情啊?
什么呀?
什么东西啊?
这个其实它在洞口里在使用的。
它在这块上。
这个东西在戴上,
你会看到它在汤带里放眼泡。
它在这里在配变。
那它在这里在冲进去。
因为它在这块额上.
你大概在试天,
Why do I feel like I'm getting more and more cussed at?
At the time, I just felt like, eh?
Why am I getting more and more wrong?
Hurry up and change it, adjust it.
Really?
I think I've had a matching shirt in my previous live stream.
Okay, now I'm going to go along with the curve.
Now it doesn't look like I'm getting more and more cussed at, right?
Now I'm going to use the curve tool to draw the pattern.
Because I feel like there are some weird spots here,
but I can't really tell where they are weird.
So I just want to adjust them.
And the more I adjust, the weirder it gets.
I'm just...
I'm just thinking, eh? Why is that?
Why is that? What exactly is the problem?
I even tried to put more pressure on him.
Eh? There's no difference.
And I'm just speechless.
I'm just thinking, why is that?
I'm obviously doing it the right way.
Oh, I got it back.
No words.
So the bottom, if you look from this side, is the bottom, right?
But since the bottom here is curved,
so the bottom of here is curved inwards.
It has to match up to the bottom.
Right...
So I was stuck here for a while.
For about 10 minutes.
So I was thinking, what on earth is going on?
It's straight.
You can only straighten it out if you use a leather cloth.
A leather cloth is very hard,
It is easy to stand up when it is in the line of the sewing line, and I added a fixing pin before, this is the main point to rely on, because it is like this after adding a fixing pin,
and then give it a little wing, add pressure, you see, I am not convinced here, I said Tingting, how can she not stand up,
I can't stand up, and then I changed the leather fabric, and I think the position of the sewing line is too flat,
no wonder, the reason I found it, it turned out to be because this head is like a question mark,
I still don't give up, I just keep adjusting it with my hands, and in the end I can't stand it, I still added a fixing pin,
I decided to bow to reality,
and then slightly change the position of this swimming pool, we will skip this part,
and then put this swimming pool into it, and then give it a frozen state,
and then we will activate all the panels, Marvelous Design does not have rendering,
rendering is only,
our sister version,
there is rendering, we don't have rendering,
then because of the butterfly knot in front of the chest, we just saw it when we simulated it,
if it is simulated, it will be unstable,
so we will put it in the form of a copy,
here we also quickly skipped,
in short, here is to add some fixing pins, and then attach the fixing pin to the virtual model,
after the copy, it will be locked together with the grid of the virtual model,
if the virtual model changes its position, these areas that are relatively unstable will follow the virtual model together,
quickly skip, here is to add the fixing pin,
and then attach the fixing pin to the virtual model,
and then there is IK, we should be able to add this IK in the future, because,
one of our sister software is IK,
there are two knots on the side of the pants,
the knot on both sides of this side, I directly use the secondary key to lock it,
you can see that since I changed the action,
these fixed pin positions, it will follow the model,
activate it again, then freeze these two steel rings,
then print out the other parts,
then give it a separate simulation,
so that its shape will be slightly modified,
because like this picture of mine,
its action is relatively large,
so we have to simulate each part separately,
so if you want to seal the virtual model this time,
you can tell me in advance,
I'm really scared,
and then because,
oh my,
hello, hello, hello, everyone,
are you still there?
anyway, remember to put this,
this,
red,
okay, okay,
because I don't know why I suddenly can't see the chats,
let me see why my,
oh, okay,
luckily I saw two chats,
for the pose,
just shift plus x,
you can change it,
thank you,
head to eat melon,
oh,
go,
you can't go there,
okay,
and get back to the beginning of the point,
say hello to the chat,
okay,
oh,
that's it,
hello,
good luck,
For example, change the fabric of the clothes, etc.
And then reduce its conflict thickness a little bit.
Thank you, thank you, thank you for your attention.
Improve the strength of the gold tail.
Because of the fan, its stretching performance is generally not very good.
But its style will be relatively loose.
So here I will let this dress, because I added a fake sewing needle before.
The fake sewing needle will also follow the virtual model.
The process of posing.
I forgot, I forgot, did I put it in the overall video?
I don't think I put it in this time.
My pose is very fast.
If it's hot, it's just...
Oh, my internet is not very good.
If it's hot, it's actually fast.
I quickly changed the sewing line to turn.
Why do you want to see the process of posing?
Actually, I have a way, but I think that if I put it out, it will...
Oh, that's why you want to see the process of posing.
You want to get off class quickly, don't you?
I want to see what happens when I do it.
I can just pose it.
I have a good look.
And then I put this butterfly in the form of a negative, leave it in order.
Then I will turn around, see if he has a bug.
You are very similar, I will show you my own style.
And then it's basically over.
Let me open the project file.
In fact, because there is no IK, so I put it.
it will be better.
It's a bit...weird.
I'm always in a symmetrical position.
And then I'll quietly tell you
that sometimes I'll go to another part of our company's software
and change its position.
Because the position in Clo is with an IK.
But it's okay.
I think we'll soon have an IK.
Because IK is actually a function we already have.
Will it be blocked like this?
Wow, the model uses this.
Will it be better like this?
But I changed this position directly in ShiftX.
And then, in fact, I didn't have this ball at first.
The back of the waist is missing.
I didn't have this ball.
Do you want to see the part where I changed the position?
I think I changed this position for a while.
And then, in fact, I didn't have this ball at first.
After I didn't have this ball,
I think the focus of the model is a bit weird.
Yes, I changed the pose at the end.
Oh my god.
If you see the time I changed the pose,
you will be speechless.
Because this pose is not a very scientific pose.
Do I usually let the whole person lie down first?
It's not that hard.
About a few minutes.
Or ten minutes.
Then I will definitely be shot.
Oh, it's okay to divide it into a batch separately.
Then I'll check it again later.
Let's see if I can find that video.
The screen recording is already relatively previous.
Oh, it feels like the white model won't be blocked.
And then when I was rendering the picture,
I found that the focus point was a bit wrong.
If...
Okay, okay.
If there is no one here,
like a sphere or something,
I feel like this person will feel very uncomfortable lying down.
What do you think?
Yes, so then I'll give it...
Eh?
Hmm?
Oh, okay.
I pressed the wrong button.
How did I say that?
I pressed it for a long time and it didn't come out.
Then I added one for it.
Like that beach volleyball.
It's like that beach volleyball.
And then since I was originally a virtual model,
I came in like this.
This is a virtual model.
And then?
This dress, it will come out by itself.
Eh?
It came out.
Thank you for your attention.
Thank you.
It's not floating.
Oh, you said this?
This?
Is there any problem?
Or is there anything wrong with this project file?
Open GPU simulation, the clothes will move through the mold
Because the GPU simulation is a little unstable
Oh, about this new feature
I can only say that it is still in development
That's right, Marvelous Designer 10.5 has jumped again
Oh, no need to complete the simulation
This computer is i9
I usually use i9 at home
i9 9900
Is it possible to participate in the calculation of models with poses?
Yes, it is possible
Or whether you are in the animation era
Or whether you have two pose models
Both are possible
If there are two poses, you can use T-pose to insert the clothes
Then you use A-pose to make a Morph Target
For example, let me find one
Look, first of all, I have a pose here
This is a pose I adjusted at the beginning
This is the pose I used later
I want to sell the graphics card
Then, for example, you want to transform
Now, for example, we have another pose
OBJ
You just import it in
Select the model model
Oh, not the model model
Select Morph Target
Then it will change the pose
Now my computer is very safe
Even starting to have some dandruff
How to join the simulation in clothes?
You have to
Wait a minute
For example, now we have a rectangular board
Then there is a fixer
You can add a row of fixers to it
Wait a minute
I see it wrong
Then, for example, there is an OBJ
After the input is entered
I choose to add
Then select copy
The original book will be weird
But you didn't draw it well
The model can be
What is it when you export
What model is it
If you import
Just choose that
How can this be
OK
There is a weight here
Open the model
It will have a weight
But because the component itself is
There is no
The component itself has no collision
So after you hang up
You have to manually
Make some adjustments to it
For the board
Generally there is no
Because even if there is a glue board
There are a lot of things you have to learn
It's better to use your hands to adjust it
Can the teacher help me see
Do I practice half-heartedly?
Can't
Da Mei Da Mei
You can't
Your family
Family can be sent out
Let's learn together
Take a look
This is OK
Da Mei Da Mei
Da Mei
Oh
Although I studied fashion in college
But I am different from the board
I am
After graduating
Just started
Just started working
I started to study well
OK
For example, now we have a board
Wait a minute
Then you type in the component
After typing in
Choose add component
Then there is a glue
See if there is glue
Glue
Ta-da
I want to stick it up
Click
After adding glue
Open the simulation
It will have a weight
Weight
Then you can change its weight on the right
For example, I give it a thousand grams
Assuming this butterfly has a thousand grams
It will hammer down
See
But because of this
The fabric itself is not sprayed
It is actually equivalent to
The point of sticking
Add a little force to it
Then you can see the whole thing
Can't hear
You asked me to hand over
How to cross-stitch?
Bye
I'm not a teacher
I'm a teacher
How to cross-stitch
I can't see
Don't think
I'm not veure
I can't see
No, it's not. This is the fixer.
The fixer can hold a piece of fabric,
and then you can move it.
This is the fixer.
What about the glue?
You can choose the position of the glue.
For example, let's change the place of the glue.
The contact area cannot be adjusted.
How can this be so flexible?
How long can it be flexible?
Oh, it's not stopping.
Oh, it's getting smaller and smaller.
Speaking of this,
let's do a scientific experiment.
Now it's moving very fast, right?
If we put its...
its internal damping...
higher.
And then we pull it.
Oh, does it feel different from before?
It seems to be almost the same.
Forget it.
It's fine.
The inside damping is much faster.
If the temperature is low,
it'll keep moving.
It's going to move longer.
So it's a bit different.
Is this a real stone?
Yes.
Farris Designer Stone.
This is a...
This is a stone.
A stone.
What is this stone?
This is...
A stone.
It's a stone.
怎么做窗帘 关于窗帘的制作方法的话 关于窗帘的制作方法的话 可以看之前有一期 关于窗帘的制作方法的话 可以看之前有一期
我来找一下啊 在教学视频有一期直播 就是做家居的那一套 我来找一下啊 在教学视频有一期直播 就是做家居的那一套
闭站无线打不开 封面是沙发还是像床一样的那一期 可以看 窗帘的话做起来还是比较快的 像窗帘这种就是属于它的版片比较大 然后它呢不会有太多层级 然后整体比较规律的版片呢 可以就直接用GPU模拟
大家还有什么问题哦 大家还有什么问题哦 有没有问题 有没有 有没有
有没有 有没有 有没有
有没有 有没有
够了 Yout per mite
够了aleb
够了 Stall
有了 Rat
有了 三个
也没有问题
没有问题的话我就要点你们
你们小心一点
我看到有一些长时间观看
但是没有打字的小朋友
我来抓你了
最近还有什么培训的活动吗
我们从来就没有做过什么培训呀
自己一个人学得好痛苦
可以先看直播视频呀
直播一般我们会分批嘛
然后我们分的二批的话一般都是
好吧
一般分的二批的话
都是这个教学视频的
你就跟着那个步骤
不可以
现在不能做到边缘完美西边面对接
但是我们可以开那个
提一个功能开发需求
让我打开看看你有什么不懂的
可以呀
你可以看了
大家看自己的项目文件里面
有没有不懂的地方
其实大家可以
加入我们的那个QQ群
然后平时里面也有很多小伙伴
会聊天呀
还有
就是平时有些交流啊什么的
开车会被封号的,所以先被我禁言一分钟,然后禁言一天,然后会被我封号的,小心一点。
虽然现在从来都没有人被封过,但是以后说不定会有的。
大家还有没有什么其他的问题呀?
或者你们想知道的一些事情呀,或者什么的。
运行下面小人旁边两个工具。
什么呀?
什么?
怎么定够了?
不够了。
请等下。
SOF会在 stoleroober吗?
不会。
不会呢?
谢谢ланlin déclarations。
谢谢 olejunic peacock behind my back.
我好忍悲。
Is it gonna be an chị Stat?
Thank you
Oh, you mean this?
Oh, this can pause actions
For example, there was an action in the beginning
Wait a second
For example, right now we have a...
Let me change to a model that looks more harmonious
For example, right now we have a model
This looks even more suspicious
There's an action
We can change a pose for it
When changing the pose
Press this to pause the pose
For example
Sometimes you just want it to be in the middle
You can pause it
Can MD be solved?
Yes, MD is about...
If you want to buy three levels
In the next...
In the next week, I might post a post
It's about...
Right now we have supported Alipay to buy
Alipay subscription
It won't be like Steam
Sorry
It won't be like before
When two objects are solved and entangled together
It's usually recommended to freeze one of them
It's best to freeze the inner layer
Then rearrange the outer layer for it
First, the entangled part
Use the select grid tool
Drag it
Select a piece
For example, suppose this piece is entangled
Then we drag it out
Drag it to the round
Because this version is now on the outer layer
Then you turn it on for simulation
It will sort it out a little
Folding angle and folding intensity are like this
Let's talk about the folding angle first
Folding angle
For example, now we have an inner layer
Then the folding angle means that
When this ...
For example, the folding angle is 0
This plate will go out
So this line will protrude out
Let's reduce it a little bit
Can you see it
This one
It will protrude in this position.
If the fold angle of this line is greater than 180,
then if you look at it from the front, it should fold in like this, so it will dig in.
The latest version is 6.0.579.
When you run it, the selection tool will automatically...
Oh, sorry.
You have to use...
This is called...
I can't remember what it's called in English.
You have to use the positional ball to hit it,
or else it will be deleted.
What?
Oh no, oh no.
Oh, you have to click on the background.
Oh no, it flipped.
I remember it wasn't working before.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
I feel like there are some bugs.
When I used to click on the simulation, it would delete 3.0.
No way, it can't be a bug.
I also forgot.
I'll try the old version later.
Anyway, this version won't delete.
In the old version, I also remember that it would delete.
Oh, yes, I remember.
It's you moving.
For example, you pull it.
Eh?
It really deleted before.
Haha, I found a bug.
The mb-tool is always a difficult object.
So, about the tool, we still recommend that you use it in other 3D software.
Um, the editor.
In 3D software, we will draw some lines on the clothes.
For example, draw a circle for it.
Okay, we're done drawing now.
After we're done drawing, we can draw a line here.
Okay, after we're done drawing, we can choose this line.
And then...
Oh, I chose the wrong line. Sorry.
For example, after we're done drawing,
we can give it a shortcut.
We can create a 3D window directly.
And then we can cut it.
This way, it's more convenient to make some cuts on the clothes.
You can also cross the board.
After you cross the board, you can cut it.
Okay, these two pieces will be dug down at the same time.
Where to adjust the air wall?
First of all, we need to adjust the surface.
It means the thickness of the air wall around the model,
not the thickness of the model.
For example, now the surface is 3D,
so the surface of the virtual model will be 3 mm thick.
The thickness of the air wall around the board,
meaning the thickness of the air wall around the board,
after we choose a board,
an increase in thickness will be made at the bottom of the attribute editor.
This is the conflict thickness option that we often talk about.
Of course, the value of the conflict thickness here is the air wall around this board.
In other words, the real thickness of the air in the middle of the clothes of the virtual model is the conflict thickness of the board itself,
plus the diameter of the model itself.
For example, this is 2.5, and then here is 3.
So the actual distance from this side to the model's skin is 2.5 plus 3, which is 5.5.
Let's see what's behind it.
Normally, the selection grid will disappear.
If it doesn't disappear...
Eh?
Hmm?
Sigh, what a bug.
Because, in general,
it will disappear, so we will choose to use a fixed point.
Generally speaking, we will use a fixed point to fix its grid position.
Do you have any other questions?
My hair is poking my eyes.
The application of folding angles.
For example, now select the edge on both sides.
Select the inner line according to the selection line.
20, 20.
And then, in the past, we...
If you want to fold this sheet...
Ah, I'm sorry.
Can I pull it together?
For example, in the past, we had to choose like this.
It's very tiring to choose one by one.
For example, if we want to fold it up,
we choose 0 here, and then...
We choose 360 here, and then it will fold up, right?
Right?
Then, if you use the fold and fold tool,
it can automatically fold.
Click the 70 point, and then double click to end.
You can see that this will automatically apply some angle of fold and cut.
We usually choose three as a group.
Then click OK to simulate.
Hey, it's folded.
And then the pink leopard pattern.
If it's on the website, you can buy it.
You can buy it.
And then it's free.
Hmm.
It seems that none of you are paying attention to our movements.
I'm sad.
That's right.
That's how you fold a lampshade.
After you're done, you draw another sheet on top.
For example, draw a sheet like this for him here.
And then,
this is the fold and fold.
This is the 70 point.
And then this is the bottom one.
Then you can see that because we have three lines, it's a group.
So when you put the mouse directly on top of it, it will be like this.
That is, it will be based on the three lines.
And then at this time, you have to choose these lines below.
Because now you choose this line.
This line is not interrupted.
Then there is no way to identify these three lines.
So we have to choose this line.
And then right click.
There is an add point to the panel line.
After you choose it, these lines will be interrupted.
See?
After you interrupt it, you use this.
This is how you use this tool.
And then,
Hey, hey, hey, this is very good.
After that, you can move this panel.
And then,
Hey,
do you understand?
How do you install the tie?
Tie...
Just use a pin to turn it around.
Or you can make a fake one.
That is our mall.
And then you can buy some clothes here in the mall.
But this shirt is free.
So why don't you download it?
This shirt was made by our last live broadcast.
Last, last live broadcast.
First, you need to make sure that all the internal lines have been right-clicked, and then
go to the extra points of the outline line, so that you can cut this whole line into
small sections.
Because this tool needs to identify these small sections, and then use this tool to
mark the point, click the starting point, click the end point.
This panel is the whole panel, that is, the whole panel.
This panel is the whole panel, that is, the belt panel that we often use.
Below here is our group panel.
Then you can see that as you move the mouse, is it three lines in a group?
It is selected in this form.
Then don't click the mouse, just move, move, move.
Hey, will it start to select?
Right?
After selecting, click here when it's done.
It will mark by itself.
Do you understand?
Do you know how to do it?
Is there anything you don't know how to do?
No, right?
Then I personally think this is a better way to use it.
For example, this is a panel.
Then.
Hmm.
You'd better fold it up first.
Fold it up first before you copy it.
Otherwise, it will have some penetrating problems.
Residual and iteration.
Eh?
I don't use it much.
Is this a simulation setting?
Is it a setting in the simulation attribute?
Ah, iteration and residual.
Don't copy it if you have nothing to do.
I also forgot.
You can flip through the manual.
In this general situation, don't change it.
It's easy to be unstable.
CG, complete state.
I think it should be residual.
It may simulate a few more times.
Let me see.
If you choose Sichuan,
it will become residual.
It should be completed after reaching a certain value.
If you just use the normal one,
iteration,
its accuracy should not be that high.
Anyway, don't adjust it yourself.
You just choose to use Sichuan here.
For Sichuan,
because the attribute of Sichuan,
it is,
when calculating the physical attribute,
it should be more accurate than the normal default.
But your simulation speed will be slower.
So in general,
we would recommend that you use the normal default.
Then when you are in animation,
it will change to animation to complete this attribute.
At this time, it is already residual.
And then,
this attribute is the most suitable,
this simulation is the most suitable for animation production.
If there is another Sichuan,
what does the type below the attribute mean?
Are you talking about this?
These are different.
GPU is GPU simulation.
GPU simulation is normal,
that is,
you usually wear normal,
3D window,
that is,
the one that is not used in simulation mode.
Complete,
that is,
animation,
to complete this,
is specially made for recording animation.
Its accuracy should be higher.
Then,
the simulation should be more stable.
But its simulation speed will be slower.
Because of your,
this,
cycle number or something,
it will increase.
Then,
the state will change when the CG is completed.
After that,
it is Sichuan.
Sichuan is the slowest simulation speed in all preset animations.
Let you feel it.
You can feel it.
If you use normal simulation to simulate,
it will fall down soon.
If you use complete to simulate,
it will be a little slower.
If you use Sichuan,
because Sichuan,
it is to match with the real world,
so it will be very,
very slow.
The simulation speed is not the more,
the better.
Because the simulation speed is equivalent to,
it will do a calculation for you in the background.
Then,
it will calculate the relatively stable one.
The more your speed,
the longer you will use it.
In short,
do not change your simulation speed out of curiosity.
Because,
the simulation speed,
the simulation speed are before you adjust the sample.
Because our predestined general is the most stable
and the most most normal state after we tested.
If you change your own,
such as simulated results,
or cg round elevation graph.
There is a possibility that there will be some problems,
or is unstable problem.
But you can,
in the user profile to change it.
Change it to your habits,
And even if you change the simulation speed, for example, now we are
Normal, normal, change its simulation speed to 5
You're just simulating at a slower speed, but the final effect of your simulation
It doesn't necessarily have a big difference from just circling once
Do you understand?
Because it's just selected in the middle of the simulation speed, the most stable one
Why does the animation animation frame disappear during animation simulation?
This is the setting
This is a little bit related to some principles
When you change the animation frame of the version, your grid also changes
Then the grid we used before
Because there are friends in the group today
That is, can the animation frame go out?
Then we asked, it's like this
Because the animation in Mother's Designer is prepared
Then after you make some changes
These animations will make some other changes
But the animation simulation period changes the animation frame
I think if you just pause and simulate
It should be ok
It will only cover what you simulated before
What is the function of the grid puller?
The function of the grid puller is like this
For example, you have a board
Give it four corners and add some fixed needles
It now has some natural wrinkles
Then when you use the grid puller
For example, now this grid puller
I am using a vertical grid puller
Your mouse is displayed as light blue
Add some of this grid puller to it
It will be collected in the middle
It will shrink a little
Can you see it?
Then it is equivalent to the current version
Will shrink very small
In the middle, its position will be pulled in
Then you can go back to it first
Then, for example, here we change the shrink rate to positive
This is not a movement
This is a grid puller
Why is the shape of the grid puller a movement?
If you give it a positive
It will have more fabric here
Why is its shape a movement?
Because in real life
Why is the grid puller called like this?
In real life
This is a bit related to clothing
For example, we sometimes
A sleeve of a piece of clothing
Let's open one
For example, this is a piece of clothing
Sometimes the sleeve
Its sleeve will be bigger
Then it will be smaller here
We will use
Is to transport
To transport
Transport this piece of board
Yes
The planning is basically like this
It's a bit tired
Transport this piece of board
Then, for example, sometimes
I'm going to change its head
Wait a minute
Can cancel the ground
Cancel the ground
Let Jimmy use the barcode memory
Let's demonstrate here
For example, sometimes
Our sleeve
This piece of board
Make it a little bigger
Then this side is not
Change a color
This color is a bit
I can't see
I can't see it clearly
I remember
Turn this off
For example, sometimes
When sewing
Is this sleeve here
Is it going to be bigger?
Make it a little more obvious
It will arch up
Then in real life
If it's when doing clothing craft
Everyone will use this
This tool
Is to use
Although it is a transport
But this operation is called
Forging and pulling
The value is negative
It's called forging
Just put this side
Forging
You use
Transport
To transport this board
When
You can
Through the hand
Pull
For example, put it here
Go to collect
Collect a little more
Put it
This operation
We call it forging
Forge
Forging
It is called forging in Chinese
After operation
This one
Because the cloth
Are all stretchable
When you use the transport
To transport it
Sometimes
For example
Hot and cold
You use your hand
To pull it
Its length
Will be shortened
It will become
For example, a negative 10
Then you look at the simulation
It will be collected
Then
For example
Sometimes
We make some suit pants
Yes
For example
When making suit pants
This length is not enough
Oh
I said it the other way around
I haven't made clothes for a long time
It's just
In the sleeve
It is often used to pull
In the suit
It is often used to roll
Sorry
My fashion teacher heard that
He wanted to hit me
Oh, my fashion teacher
Hit me directly
For example
Like the sleeve here
Because I suddenly sit down
I feel a little wrong
Because in general
It's forging pants
When the length of the pants
Is not right
Some parts will be forged
Then for example
This sleeve
Its length is now
Equivalent
Let's assume its length
Is equivalent
Then
Through this
Pull
That is, the number of pull-pulls
It's straight
It's red
Right
Then
You just
Here
Forge
Then
Because it's straight
So
These nets
Will be
Increased by nine percent
It will have
More quantity
Here
In real life
It is
For example
There is a piece of cloth
Is like this
For example
There is a piece of cloth
Is like this
Then you
Hold it
I'm afraid
How does it work
Just like this
Pull a little longer
This is called
Pull
Turn it
Sorry
Just pull it more
This is called pull
Turn the respond
For this
I'm going to make the amount of the material a little bigger
For the turtle, I'm going to put it...
Eh, put it away
The turtle
No, it's not stuck
I accidentally pulled it
So when you're using the turtle handle
You can imagine it
When you use the handle
That is, the positive number
It will have more amount here
It suddenly became a chicken leg sleeve
It's really good
Suddenly
Why did it suddenly become a sheep leg sleeve
This
Hurry up and tell the group
What to do if you want to learn how to make a sheep leg sleeve
Let me show you the grid
Look, the grid has become bigger
Can you see it?
It's pretty good looking
Did you forget about it?
This is a male model
Not only did I use this
Not only did I use purple
I also used
Hey, kids, don't make a mess
I'm speechless
Why is it always
When there's no need
Suddenly
A new way of making
Why is it always
It's not like this
I'm speechless
Usually
It's to make this
Make this board bigger
How do you feel
It looks better
I'm speechless
But don't use too much grid
If you use too much grid
Your computer will run out
You see
I was fast
And then I used the grid
And it was broken
I understand
Take the group
Take a look at the previous live
The previous live had a glue
The previous live related to the group
There is glue
I said there is no problem
Learned
Brothers
Learned to play fair
Well done
I am a ordinary
I am a ordinary genius
But your computer will run
Well, that's all for today
My friends
Thank you for watching
Please subscribe
拜拜
拜拜 拜拜 拜拜 拜拜 拜拜 拜拜
大家再见 再见
拜拜
不辛苦 不辛苦
大家有什么问题可以加我们的群
然后问一下
客气啦 客气啦
有问题的话可以
左下角有我们的那个这里
有我们的官方群号
So add our group chat and ask questions
Thank you everyone for watching the live stream so late at night
Thank you everyone
Then we'll see you in the next live stream, bye bye
Bye bye
I can't let my beauty disappear, bye bye
Bye everyone, good night, bye bye
If you have any questions, you can ask us in the group chat, bye bye